{
    "subject": "resource/Construcciones_Aeron\u00e1uticas_SA",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Spain",
    "human_readable": "Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA is located in Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9786840081214905,
            "question": "Where is Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8940966725349426,
            "question": "In what country is Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7948846817016602,
            "question": "What industry does Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7920926213264465,
            "question": "What type of company is Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7194480895996094,
            "question": "What is the history of Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7142220735549927,
            "question": "Who are the key people leading Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6848187446594238,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges facing Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6750773191452026,
            "question": "Are there any famous products or projects associated with Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6082070469856262,
            "question": "Does Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA have any subsidiaries or branches?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.607745349407196,
            "question": "What is the future outlook for Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA is located in Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7267_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA have any subsidiaries or branches?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7267_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous products or projects associated with Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7267_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges facing Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7267_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7267_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA is located in Spain\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Construcciones Aeron\u00e1uticas SA (CASA) was founded in Seville, Spain, and later became part of Airbus operations based in Spain. This supports the statement that CASA is located in Spain."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}